to
live like say welcome brothers and
sisters to another Wednesday question
and answer will we open up with the Ten
Commandments that God commanded the
world to keep brother
tanzel and God spake all these words
saying I am the Lord thy God which have
brought thee out of the land of Egypt
out of the house of bondage thou shall
have no other gods before me thou not
make un thee any Graven image or any
likeness of anything that is in heaven
the above or that is in the earth
beneath or that is in the water under
the Earth thou shall not bow down
thyself to them nor serve them for for
the Lord thy God am a jealous God
visiting the iniquities of the fathers
upon the children unto the third and
fourth generation of them that hate me
and showing Mercy unto thousands of them
that love me and keep my Commandments
thou shall not take the name of the Lord
thy God in vain for the Lord will not
hold him Guiltless that taketh his name
in vain remember the Sabbath day to keep
it holy six days shall thy labor and do
all thy work but the seven day is the
Sabbath of the Lord thy God and that
thou shall not do any work thou nor thy
son nor thy daughter thy man servant nor
thy maid servant nor thy cattle nor thy
stranger that is within thy gates for
six days the Lord made Heaven and Earth
the sea and all that in them is and
rested the seventh day wherefore the
Lord blessed the Sabbath day and
hollowed it honor thy father and thy
mother that thy days may be long upon
the land which the Lord thy God giveth
thee thou shall not kill thou shall not
commit adultery thou shall not steal
thou not bear false witness against thy
neighbor thou not cover thy neighbor's
house thou not cover thy neighbor's wife
nor his man's servant nor his maid
servant nor his Ox nor his ass nor
anything that is thy neighbors we read
Exodus 21-17 may the Lord have a
blessing to the reading of his words in
Jesus name we pray amen
amen so here on question and answer you
can ask us a question and we'll answer
it according to the King James Bible and
if we cannot find the answer we will
seek further counsel to bring you an
answer at a later time keep in mind that
all V questions will not be answered and
all long scripture questions will not be
answered for time sake but we make be
able to point you in the direction of a
DVD or CD that you can purchase by
calling office so please be as direct as
possible with your questions out of the
King James Bible so we can be as direct
as possible with our answers out of the
King James Bible no other Bibles will be
acknowledged on this program also keep
in mind that this is a live stream and
you may begin to send in your questions
at this time even questions that pertain
to everlasting life we're just asking
that you keep your questions to a two
scripture minimum but let me introduce
you to family that's on the panel this
evening we got brother Dre good evening
brother Julius good evening everybody
brother tanzel good
evening sister Deborah good
evening and we have sister Casey with us
as well as the guest caller and I'm
brother Cornell sister Deborah let us
begin with our first question of the
evening yes uh there are several
questions that will be answered first
before getting into tonight's Q&A so
read the Bible daily as can you please
explain Revelations 17 verse 16 will the
EU turn against the mother Church I'm
guessing this is during or after the
Great
Tribulation all right Revelation 17 and
161 zel let's go there by will the EU
turn against the mother church when you
get there brother read that verse 16 and
the guest caller will take it from
there and the T horns was thou sers upon
the Beast these shall hate the and
shall make her desolate and naked and
shall eat her flesh and burn her with
fire well you know this is during the
Great Tribulation not after because in
the end of the Great Tribulation you
ain't going to be doing nothing because
the Lord is going to deal with them but
the only thing that I can see here I
don't have no scripture for it but the
only thing I can see here like used to
be in the old days when you had more
than one po
this pope mooved from Vatican City and
moved to
Jerusalem they will probably try to set
up another Pope or will set up another
Pope and what this Pope does in
Jerusalem is going to stick these 10
Nations on them and burn get Vatican
City
down that
is my belief but I cannot read no
scripture for it
and the reason he going to do it is
because uh they going he going say hey
poop is you know he's in he's in the
temple of God now so what you're doing
setting up somebody else in his
place and that has happened in the past
you had more than one pole that's all I
have to say all right we hope that
shares some light for you as we continue
to move on to our next question next
question Cal said
what does Genesis 6 verse3 mean if Aaron
Sarah and Abraham live over 120 years
old if you live over 120 years old what
does it mean brother Julius let's go to
the Bible and read that
scripture 10 Genesis
6 Genesis 6 and three and if you had
start from the top it'll tell you that
uh men as men begin to multiply on the
face of the Earth they became more
wicked and more wicked let's look at
what the Lord felt about that go
ahead and the Lord said my spirit shall
not always drive with man for that he
also is flesh yet his days shall be 120
years so the Lord cut this man did man
used to live hundreds and hundreds of
years and but the more the long they
live they they became more and more
wicked so he said they are flesh and
flesh is corrupted corrupt and can be
corrupted let's go let me show you what
I'm talking about let's go to he said
yet his day shall be 120 years let's go
to Psalms Psalm remember he remember the
book said for he that he is also flesh
he's also flesh let's go to Psalm
Psalm
78 that's where I want to go because you
named three righteous Servants of God
Aaron Sarah and Abraham righteous before
the eyes of the Lord Spirit of the Lord
was with
them I'm sorry I'm sorry Psalm 90 Psalm
90 we're gonna hold that 78 Psalm 90
tanzel Psalm 90 and Look What the Lord
said at verse 10
Psalm 90 and verse 10 when you get it go
ahead brother the days of our years are
three score years and 10 uhhuh and if by
reason of strength they be four score
Years yet is their strength labor and
sorrow for it is soon cut off and we fly
away the Lord say the years of our days
are three score 10 that's 70 years old
and if you live to be 80 that's a
blessing but it's still by reason the
strength if you live above that that is
the mercy and grace of God because you
can do that so now back up to
Psalms let's go to
Psalm
78 Psalm 78 and I want to pick it up at
verse let's look at this corruptible
flesh Psalm 78 and
17 when you get it go
ahead and they sin yet more against him
by provoking the most high in the
wilderness this is Israel in the
wilderness Flesh and Blood verse 37
why but for their heart was not right
with him neither were they standies in
this Covenant that mean that his Spirit
didn't dwell with them continue at 38
all the way all the way to
39 but he being full of compassion
forgave their iniquity and destroyed
them not yet many a Time turned he his
anger away and did not stir up all his
wrath why for he remembered that they
were but flesh uhuh a wind that passeth
away and cometh not again so in this
Flesh and Blood body you your you're not
gonna always your every meditating
waking thought is not gonna be on God
because we flesh that's why the
scriptures tell you if we sin willfully
you understand because uh we flesh and
blood and we're capable of sin so that
mean that the Lord Spirit not going to
always dwell with us that's the best I
can do with
that all right thank you for that
brother hope that answer that question
sister
deor yes next question is brother
Anthony horsey asked for you to shed
some light on first John 5 versus 16 and
17 first John
5 vers 16 and 17 brother Julius share
some light let's go tzel first John 5
bend your Bible to First John 5 and be
reading at verse
16 go ahead if any man see his brother
sin of sin which is not unto death he
shall ask and he shall give him life for
them that sin not unto death uhhuh but
there is a sin unto death I do not say
that he shall pray for
it all unrighteousness is sin and there
is a sin not unto death now first John
34 says that sin is the transgression of
the law but there is a sin that is not
unto death let's go and read about it
because there is a sin that is not unto
death and there is a sin that is unto
death Matthew the 12th
chapter Matthew chapter
12 and we gonna pick this up uh brother
tenzel Matthew
12 and let's pick it up at verse 31
Matthew 12 and 31 will you get it
brother go ahead and read
it wherefore I say unto you all man of
sin and blasphemy shall be forgiven unto
men because it can be forgiven go ahead
but the blasphemy against the the Holy
Ghost shall not be forgiven unto men uh
and bling against the Holy Spirit or the
Holy Ghost shall not be forgiven in this
world nor the world to come go ahead
brother and whosoever speaketh a word
against the son of man it shall be
forgiven him uhuh whosoever speaketh
against the Holy Ghost it shall not be
forgiven him neither in this world
neither in the world to come so
therefore Blas mean when you put your
insert yourself in the uh in in the seat
of God and you make the word of God a
lie so therefore that blasphemy that uh
can be that cannot be forgiven is when
you calling the word of God a outright
lie so now but there's all manner of
sins shall be forgiven you could be
forgiven because you could repent from
that right there but blasphemy against
the Holy Spirit
calling the word of God Al cannot be
forgiven in this world neither the world
will come and so you know you tell
that's what you tell people all man of
sin can be
forgiven but blasphemy against the Holy
Spirit cannot be forgiven in this world
neither the world of come anybody want
to add to
that yeah you you know the truth and
tell a lie you asking for it gu call up
let's go to Romans the first chapter and
get an example of that yes
sir yes
sir Romans chapter one and let's see I
think we going we're going to start it
at you want to start this at uh I think
it's at 18 yes
sir 1 and 18 start reading when you get
there for the wrath of God is revealed
from Heaven against all ungodliness and
unrighteousness of men who hold the
truth in unrighteousness wow now that's
the key right there that's the key right
there who hold the truth in
unrighteousness they know the truth
right but they are for their own benefit
keep reading because that which may be
known to God is manifested in them for
God ha showed it unto them uhuh go for
the invisible things of him from the
creation of the world are clearly seen
being understood by the things that are
made
even as eternal power in
Godly so that they are without
excuse they even understand the eternal
power about God how he been around and
the godhead know that's
right these because he's shown it to
them these are informed people go with
because that when they knew God they
glorify him not as God neither were
thankful but became vain in their
imagination and their foolish Hearts
darkened professing themselves to be
wise they became fools and change glory
of the uncorruptible god into an image
made like to corruptible men and to
birds and for footed beast and creeping
things wherefore God also gave them up
to uncleanness through the lust of their
own F Hearts to dishonor their own
bodies between themselves
uhuh who change the truth of God into a
lie
worship that's right and change the
truth of God unto a lie and worship and
serve the creature more than the Creator
who was blessed forever
amen go ahead for this cause God gave
them up unto vow affection for even
their women did change the natural use
into that which is against
nature and likewise
also the men leaving the natural use of
the woman burned in their one towards
another a lot of turned homosexual
because they knew better and God did
this to them but go ahead and read men
with men working that which is unseenly
and receiving in themselves that
recompense of their error which was
me and even as they did not like to
retain God in their knowledge God gave
them over to a rep probate mind to to do
those things which are not convenient W
now that's when you get a rep probate
mind it's over with ain't no coming back
that's
right now that is the sin that sin
against the Holy Ghost is when you hold
the truth and unrighteousness and use it
for your benefit and not but for the
benefit of God God give that
rep you finished because you just stand
against the Holy
Ghost thank you gu caller nail right
nailed it hope that answered your
question there as we continue to move on
H yes he also ask is there uh any
scriptures that I can use to prove that
the Holy Ghost is an angel who stands in
the presence of God and bring the
message and he also want to know and
what did the Lord mean when he told
Moses to tell them I am that I
am all right brother Dre can you share
some light on this question here yes sir
let's go to um Exodus
23 Exodus
23 and we gonna pick it up at verse 20
Exodus 23 and 20 Tel read it when you
get
it behold I sent an angel before thee to
keep thee in the way and to bring thee
into the plate which I have
prepared go ahead bew of him and obey
his voice provoke him not for he will
not pardon your transgression for my
name is in him so this Angel is coming
in the name of the Lord he is not coming
in his own name he say beware of him
obey his voice the message that he's
bringing is from the Lord so now let's
go to Isaiah
63 is Isaiah 63 and we going to pick it
up at verse
7 we we see him bringing a message but
we going to see where where he's
standing
at read verse seven and we gonna skip to
verse n Go ahead brother when you get
it I will mention the loving kindness of
the Lord and the Praises of the Lord
according to all that the Lord have
bestowed on us and the great goodness
towards the house of Israel which he ha
bestowed on them according to his
mercies and according to the multitude
of his loving kindness get down the nine
and in all their Affliction he was
afflicted and the angel of his presence
saved them in his love and in his pity
he redeemed them now you know go ahead
go
ahead and he beareth them and carried
them all the days of old notice that
this Angel is the angel of his presence
but let's see what else he's called here
go ahead verse 10 but they rebell and
Vex his holy
spirit therefore he was turned to be
their enemy and he fought against them
so this is also called a holy spirit
because angels are spirit and if they
kept their first estate they're holy now
let's go to Luke the first chapter Luke
the first chapter and we going to read
verses 18 and
19 when you get it go ahead
brother Luke 1
18 and 19 and Zachariah said unto the
angel so where shall I know this for I
am an old man and my wife well stricken
in years uhuh and the angel answered and
said unto him I am Gabriel that stand in
the presence of God and am sent to speak
unto thee and to show thee these Glad
Tidings see this angel said I am Gabriel
that stand in the presence of God so
here you have it this Angel is coming to
bring Glad Tidings which is a message he
stands in the presence of God and this
is what he's doing now as far as your
other question let's go to
Exodus the third chapter sister Deborah
can you repeat that question that other
part yes the question was what did the
Lord mean when he told Moses to tell
them I am that I
am okay let's go to Exodus the thir
chapter read verses 14 and 15 brother
when you get
it and God said unto Moses I am that I
am and he said th sh thou say unto the
children of Israel I am have sent me
unto you uhhuh go ahead and God said
over unto Moses thus sh thou say unto
the children of Israel Lord God of your
fathers the god of Abraham the god of
Isaac and the god of Jacob have S me
unto you this is my name forever and
this is my Memorial unto all generations
so this is what he telling you I am the
god of Abraham the god of Isaac and the
god of Jacob right is who sent who was
sent let's go to uh one other place
let's go to Matthew
22 and read verse
32 go ahead brother when you get it I am
the god of Abraham and the god of Isaac
and the god of Jacob God is not the god
of the dead but of the living so this is
who this is I am that I am this is the
god of Abraham the god of Isaac and the
god of Jacob I hope that
helped yes sir brother the the god that
called the end from the beginning yes
sir all right thank you for that
brother as we continue to move on yes
being elf as is their reference to the
intercessors of the Bible being the
final
intercessors or can intercessors still
exist for any help with
interpretation as the prophets and the
prophet
prophetes did in the
Bible all right guess carer can you
share some light on that
question first thing is you can't you
don't have a bunch of
intercessors Moses was an
intercessor and the one that was made
like unto Moses well he is the
intercessor now intercessors just don't
pop up like that let's go into Isaiah
the 59th
chapter and we're going to read one and
two first and we going to start skipping
Isaiah 59 and one and
two behold the Lord's hand is not short
that it cannot say neither his ear heavy
that it cannot hear but your iniquities
have separated between you and your God
your sins have hid his face from you
that he would not
hear I skip down to 13 and read the 16
look at some of these sins go
ahead and transgression and lying
against the Lord and depart away from
our God speaking oppression and Revolt
conceiving and uttering from the heart
heart words of
falsehood and judgment is turned away
backwards and Justice standeth a far off
for truth is falling in the streets and
Equity cannot
enter that is the condition of the earth
keep reading yeah truth faileth and he
that depart from Evil maketh himself
will pray and the Lord saw it and it
displeased him that there was no
judgment and he saw that there was no
man and wonder that there was no
intercessor therefore his arm brought
salvation unto him and his
righteous he saw that there was no man
and there was no intercessor over the
whole earth he couldn't find nobody that
could stand in the gap for this man so
what he did he did it himself who is the
arm of the Lord Jesus right so his arm
did what read that
again he saw that there was no man in
wonder that there was no intercessor
therefore his arm brought salvation unto
him now that was verse 16 right that's
right what what so what happen skip down
to verse
20 and the Redeemer shall come to Zion
and unto them that turn from
transgression in Jacob sayeth the Lord
now so who is the Redeemer Jesus where
did he came he came to Jerusalem that's
why he said in first St John 1 and 1
chapter you said he came to his own and
his own receive him not so he is the
intercessor that's right and he is the
one that is bleading your cause let's go
first John 2 chapter 1 and
2 first John 2 1 and two
uhhuh okay first John
2 one and
to my little children these things right
I unto you that ye sin not and if any
man sin we have an advocate with the
father Jesus Christ the
righteous and he is the propitiation of
our sins and not for ours only but also
for the sins of the whole
world here The Advocate sitting right
there at the right hand of the father
and the Lord lets you know that he the
only one that can be that can stand in
the gap for you one last place Isaiah 53
read verse 11 and 12 it's talking about
Jesus Isaiah
53 that's
right y 11 11 and
12 he shall see of the travail of his
soul and shall be satisfied but his
knowledge shall my righteousness serve
and justify many but he shall bear their
iniquities therefore will I divide him a
portion with the great and he shall
divide the spoil with the strong because
he have poured out his soul unto death
and he was numbered with the
transgressors and he Beed the sin of
many and made intercession for the
transgressors so that's Jesus there
ain't no men intercession only one was
an intercessor was Moses after that it
was Jesus that's why Moses told Israel
the Lord thy God shall raise up a
prophet from among your brethren like
unto me all that who will not hear that
Prophet will get cut off there no bu of
intercessor just
one and he didn't come from among
men he had to become a man right that's
all I have to say all right thank you
for that we hope that aned your question
as we move on to our next question yes
Zion says it was mentioned right before
Christ comes they will build a temple
and place the Pope in it is it the
current pope or another and also how
will he make a statue
talk all right
guess caller is it the current pope or
another and how did he make a statue
walk and
talk answer both of those questions we
have to wait until it
happen all right we will wait and
see all right we're moving on to our
next question yes we can talk right
here uh uh here at asked is there a
difference between a Hebrew Israelite
and an
Israelite let's talk about it brother
Julius is there a difference Hebrew
Israelite and a Israelite no one of the
same
people that's
it all right we go keep it moving from
there yes moving on Mrs shortcase
strawberry and as will Gentiles also be
brought to the
Wilderness will you find some Gentile
Gentiles out in the wilderness brother
Julius absolutely you
will let's go to Exodus the 12th
chapter is the Lord sprung Israel out of
Egypt we have to remember God is no
respector of
persons he created man he said when when
he created this man he said let make man
in our image after our likeness all of
us right Exodus 12 and let's read verse
37 the book calls them strangers but
they uh uh the book calls them strangers
it was a mixed multitude even some of
the
Egyptians pick it up at verse uh Exodus
123 read 37 12 and 37 when you get it go
ahead brother and the children of Israel
journeyed from Ramsey to suko about six
00,000 on foot that were men beside
children uhhuh and a mixed multitude
went up also with them and flocks and
herbs even very much
C the book says a mixed multitude in
other places they call them
strangers remember uh on your own you
can read John 3:16 for God so loved the
world that he gave his only begotten son
that whosoever will right let him come
believe on him should not perish but
have everlasting life so yes that answer
is yes Gentiles also we brought to the
Wilderness that's all I
got all
right thank you for that brother we're
gonna move on with a time check sister
yes time is 803 Miss W says in Matthew
25 ver 24 and
25 could you please open my
understanding
all right brother Dre can you open up
Miss weight's
understanding yeah let's go to that
Matthew 25 and we're gonna read down
into it let's start at verse 14 read
verses 14 and
15 and let's go come on brother for the
Kingdom of Heaven is as a man traveling
into a far country who called his own
servants and delivered unto them his
goods and
and unto one he gave five talents to
another two and to another one to every
man ACC Koy to his several ability and
straightway took his journey this is a
parable he's speaking but man travel he
he but he delivered to them his goods
and he gave and and one he gave five
talents another two and another one one
you know uh uh our
talents a man's a man's or woman's gifts
are their talents right gift they have
that that's that's their talents but we
just read verse 15 Read
16 then he that had received the five
talents went and traded with the same
and made them also five T talents okay
now skip down to verse 24 now
then he which had received the one Tyler
came and said Lord I knew thee that thou
are hard man reaping where thou has not
sown and Gathering where thou has not
strong I was afraid and wouldn't hear
thy talent in the earth so Lo there thou
Hast that is thine so this man had a
talent the one talent and instead of him
using that talent that gift that he had
and he just hid it in the
earth six go
ahead his Lord answered and said unto
him thy Wicked and slothful servant thou
knew that I reap where I sold it not and
gather where I have not strong now skip
down to verse
28 take therefore the talent from him
and give it unto him which have t
talents go ahead for unto everyone that
have shall be given and he shall have
abundance but from him that haveth not
shall be taken away even that which he
have go ahead and cast ye the
unprofitable servant into out of
Darkness there should be weeping and
nashing of teeth yeah you got a gift you
got a talent you use it to to bring
forth fruit but let's go to uh Ephesians
4 now Ephesians 4
Ephesians 4 and pick it up at verse
eight
brother when you get it go ahead and
read wherefore he said when he Ascend up
on high he led captives cap captivity
captives and gave gifts unto men gave
gifts onto men he gave you this word he
blessed you with a way to bring it skip
down to verse
11 and he gave some Apostles and some
prophets and some evangelists and some
pastors and
teachers for the Perfection of the
Saints for the work of the ministry for
the edifying of the body of
Christ till we all come in the UN Unity
of faith of the faith and of the
knowledge of the Son of God unto a
perfect man unto the measure of the St
statue of the fullness of Christ so this
is what when when you given that you you
deal with it you make it known you take
that gift that he got and you bring
forth
fruit hope that that helps if anybody
want to
add yeah yeah thank you for that brother
Dre we know that uh many many members
make up the body don't yes
sir goad you have something tel no no no
no just agreeing oh okay all right we
hope that answered your question as we
move on to our next one uh yes and the
time is 808 Mrs shortcase strawberry
asks is faith without work
dead
absolutely faith without works is dead
because a lot of times faith can be just
mouth and no action so yeah faith
without works is dead t there just like
Kool-Aid with no
sugar so let's go to that James the uh
the second chapter James the second
chapter and let's pick it up at that
verse 14 and read how the Lord is going
to say that you can have all this Faith
but if you ain't got no Works to put
behind it then hey you just talking and
ain't walking and that don't profit
you pick it up brother James 2 pick it
up at at verse 14 and go right
ahead what doth it profit my brethren
though a man say he have faith and have
not works can Faith save him by S go
ahead if brother sister be naked and
destitute of daily food and one of you
say unto them depart in peace be ye
warmed and filled not withstanding ye
give them not those things which are
needful to the body but do Propet and
that's a good question because if
somebody is hungry and and really needs
you and you tell them I'mma pray that
you be filled how about you do some
works and help them to get filled right
go ahead brother Reed even so faith if
it have not works is dead being alone
even so if you have faith and you don't
have no Works hey it's dead being all by
itself skip down to verse 20 brother and
let's back that up
but with thou know oh vain man thy faith
without works is dead there you go again
go ahead was not Abraham Our Father
justified by works when he had offered
Isaac his son upon the altar yep he put
some works for it go ahead see as thou
how Faith wroth with his works and by
works was Faith made perfect yep once
you do your works and hey your faith can
show that you believe in God God that's
what Abraham did didn't he y That's
Right read and the scripture was
fulfilled which said which said Abraham
believed God and it was ined unto him
for
righteousness and he was called the
friend of God yes I know we all shooting
for that gold tanzel that's right read
do you see then how that by works a man
is Justified and not by faith only gotta
ask some Works go ahead
likewise also was not Rahab the harot
justified by works when she had received
the messages and had sent them out
another
way for
as go ahead for as the body without the
spirit is dead so faith without works is
dead also so it even mentioned Rahab the
Harlot who you know when she helped the
brothers Escape she believed that hey
that she could be delivered by them and
sure enough that's what happened and
just as the body without the breath is
dead so if you got faith and you don't
have no works that's dead also right so
yes is faith without works dead most
certainly and that's all I
got and we hope that that aned your
question as we move on to our next one
yes moving on the time is a 12 McGee
asked can we celebrate
birthdays and if so what can we not do
on
birthday all right it's a very popular
question about you know people always
asking can they celebrate their
birthdays because they went and read in
the Bible where Pharaoh on his birthday
he hung his chief Butler his CH Chief
Baker on his birthday and then her Rob
head to John the Baptist so people say
you can't celebrate your birthday
because those acts was done but hey you
don't have to do nothing wrong or evil
on your
birthday let's go to um let's go to John
um 14 John
14 because what's wrong with being
thankful that God gave you 12 more
months or 365 days what's wrong with
that
when you get there brotherr John 14 John
14 pick it up at that verse uh 15 this
is what you have to do even on your
birthday you ask what can and what can't
you do verse 15 go
ahead if you love me keep my
Commandments you take God Commandments
with you therefore you won't get in no
trouble on your birthday skip down to
verse uh
21 he that have my Commandments and keep
them he it is that loveth me he that
loveth me shall be loved of my father
and I will love him and will manifest
myself to him yeah we need that love
Tanz let's get down to verse
24 he that loveth me not keepeth not my
Saints and the word which ye hear is not
mine but the Father which send me so if
you don't if you don't love the Lord and
you want to go out and do everything
your flesh tell you to do on your
birthday then you don't have no love but
let's go to John First John 3 First John
3 you can have fun on your on your
birthday but it's got to be clean fun
don't get yourself in
trouble First John 3
like Julius said earlier 120 years man
we can't even imagine that can we Julius
no sir ver John 3 pick it up at at verse
four go ahead whosoever commit sin
transgress transgresseth also the
law is the transgression of the law
right stay within the law on your
birthday go ahead
and ye know that he was manifest to take
away our sins and in him is no sin one
more verse whosoever abideth in him
sinth not whosoever sinth have not seen
him neither know him so you keep your
birthday all clean enjoy thank God and
um make sure you keep those Commandments
that's all I got
all right I hope that answered your
question there we moving on to the next
yes the time is 816 Valencia asked who
is kind of ban in Amos 1
verse2 Amos 1 verse1 12 who is this kind
of a Shan brother
Dre yeah I I think well Amos 1 verse2 is
not talking about the kind of Bashan but
I think you talking about Amos 4 verse1
so let's go to Amos 4
verse1 and we going to read that read
that when you get it
t hear this word ye kind of basan that
are in the mountain of Samaria which
oppress the poor which crush the needy
which say to their masters bring and let
us drink so this is this is actually
talking about women
that but they're lacking to liken to uh
cows of
Bashan
and they oppress the poor crush the
needy and say to their husbands bring us
drink you know so it's it's it's a
little bit more to it that meets the eye
uh the the kind is a cow and it's
talking about more than one per say this
was the attitude of the people but read
a little bit more of that brother read
verses 2 and
three the Lord God have sworn by his
Holiness that Lo the day shall come upon
you that he will take you away with
hooks and your Prosper Prosperity with
Fish Hooks go
ahead and you shall go out at the
breaches every cow at that which is
before her
and ye shall cast them into the palace
sayeth the Lord okay that's that's all I
can give you on that if anybody want to
add I had a little bit more but I don't
I don't have it in front of me at the
moment all right that was a good catch
on that uh Amos 4 that's where they
meant to go brother yes sir all right
thank you for that hope that answered
that question as we move on to our next
yes time is 8:18 Jeffrey Meyer says if I
keep all of the 10 commandments and keep
my garments clean how then am I a sinner
and the scriptures given are Hebrews 8
verse 12 and Micah 7 verse
19 right Hebrews 8 and 12 is the first
one yes all right
Denzel don't you uh pick up that Hebrews
8 verse2 about if you keep the
Commandments and your garments clean how
are you still a sinner go ahead my
brother Hebrews 8 and 12 and the guest
caller will take it from
there for I will be merciful to their
unrighteousness and their sins and their
iniquities will I remember no
more and the other scripture is Micah 7
verse
19 all right did um did you want to
expound on that Hebrews guess
caller read
Michael all right you want to go to
Michael 7
and9 Michael 7
and9 he will turn again he will have
compassion upon us he will subdue to our
iniquity
and thou will cast all their sins into
the depths of the
sea now both of them we saying is
telling you that if you repent then the
Lord and stop sinning then the Lord will
be merciful unto you but as long as you
keep the Commandments then uh uh you
cannot be a sinner go to First John 3
and4
when you get
there first John 3 and
4 whosoever committeth sin transgresseth
also the law for sin is the
transgression of the
law so when you repent then the Lord
will be merciful for you to you and
won't hold your sins against you and
then if you are keeping the Commandments
then you are no longer committing sin
and you are no longer a sinner you been
wased all I have to say all
right hope that that ansed your question
there as we continue to move on to our
next question uh yes Mr short Cas
strawberry and what prayer can I say to
motivate myself to read God's word when
I don't feel like
it well the whole book is is good for
when you don't feel like it and if
you've never read it from cover to cover
you should set that up as a challenge
for yourself from Genesis to Revelation
you should read the whole book but let's
go into um Second Timothy the 2
chapter and let this resonate with you
very well second Timothy 2 and pick it
up at verse 15 brother read that one
verse study to show thyself approved
unto God a Workman that needeth not to
be ashamed rightly dividing the word of
Truth so even though your flesh don't
feel like it hey you should be studying
to show yourself approved unto God and
appreciate this great word of eternal
life that he has laid out Lord say
sometimes studying is a weariness over
the FL flesh but you got to shake
yourself and get it to this race for
eternal life now let's go into uh Psalms
119 let's go Psalms
119 because if you understand in this
word and you are being told the truth
you have a whole lot to be thankful
for Psalm 119 brother pick it up at
verse 33
give you a little food right here go
ahead teach me oh Lord the way of thy
statues and I shall keep it unto the
end give me understanding and I shall
keep thy law yeah I shall observe it
with my whole heart yes make me to go in
the path of thy Commandments for therein
do I Delight so you have to go in and
and read this word so that you can get
some of this good food applied to
yourself skip down read 43 and
44 and take not Thy Word Of Truth
utterly out of my mouth for I have hoped
in thy judgment yes so shall I keep thy
law continually forever and ever because
you don't want too many days to go by
when you don't feel like it and you just
don't read the word read that last verse
49 for me and that'll be it remember the
word unto thy servant upon which thou H
has caused me to Hope and you know if
you know this word of God that you got a
good reason to read it even when you
don't feel like it because hey reading
the Bible is never something that you
say I wish I hadn't done that so get in
there and read that book pray and thank
God that he has allowed for you to see
these words of eternal life that's all I
got
well I give you a direct
prayer yes sir make all
right Psalm 51 vers 10 through 12 yes
sir yes sir yeah yeah
sir Psalm 51
10-2 create me a clean heart oh God and
renew a right Spirit Within Me and cast
me not away from thy presence and take
not thy Holy Spirit from
me unto me the joy of thy salvation and
uphold me with thy free spirit
yes do not his Clean Heart the Lord say
that's the prayer you do if you do that
you make that prayer then he then he
will give you the mind to study because
you have a clean heart and you'll be
about his word that's
you should
make amen all all right and we uh we
hope the best for you all right let's
move on to our next question sister yes
we are now into tonight's Q&A for July
the 3
2024 The Air I Breathe ask for you to
explain to be absent from the body is to
be present with the Lord aren't we in a
deep sleep when we
die all right
so guest caller um I want to know are
you in a deep sleep when we
die yeah but it's called
Dead correct now let's go and find show
you what what the what what it mean be
absent with the Lord you know and and uh
uh absence absent from the body and and
be with the Lord first thing is you got
to understand one
thing if uh uh to be absent with the
Lord that is to be that mean to be in
his kingdom it's not walking around in
heaven you can't come outside of your
body so let's show you what it mean
because Paul if he could be ABS with the
Lord then he would have got up out of
this body and and he going to show you
that he can't even do that let's go to
Romans the 7th
chapter and read verse
24 7 and verse
24 oh Wretched Man that I am who shall
deliver me from the body of this
death now if he could get out of that
body and be AB with the Lord he would
but he
cannot okay and the reason can't so when
you want to be aing with the Lord you
got to be in his kingdom so you can't
carry this body with you go to First
Corinthians 15 chapter and read verse
49-
54 and as we have borne the image of the
Earthly we shall also bear the image of
the heavenly
now this I say Brethren that flesh and
blood cannot inherit the kingdom of God
neither do inherit
inup you we are Flesh and Blood
can't go ahead oh I show you a mystery
we shall not all sleep but we shall all
be
changed in a moment in the twinkling of
an eye at the last Trump for the trumpet
shall sound and the dead shall be raised
incorruptible and we shall be
changed but this corruptible must put on
incorruption and this Mortal must put on
immortality so when this corruptible
shall put have put on incorruption and
this Mortal shall have put on
immortality then shall be brought to
pass the same that is written death is
swallowed up in
Victory so now the only way you can be
absent from this body and present with
the Lord is when the Lord bring his
kingdom down that's talking about the
father's Kingdom and flesh and blood
cannot enter into that Kingdom so this
out of body experience and and uh
floating up and looking down on yourself
that ain't nothing but folk
l so Paul said he he's really saying
I'll be glad when I ain't got to carry
this Flesh and Blood body that's trying
to murder me right and when I can make
the change and get my new body one just
like God and be God that's what I really
want to
be that's simply all he's
saying that's all have to say about that
all right hope that answered your
question there our next question next
question KJ wants explanation of the
secret of the Lord in Psalms 25 verse4
who also please explain first corini 1
verse 7 and
27 the foolishness of preaching the
gospel and the foolish things of the
world so Psalms 25
verse4 they want an explanation of the
secret of the Lord and then to explain
First Corinthians Ians 1 verse 7 and
27 all
right go read
it of Psalm 25 and
14 yes the secret of the Lord is with
them that fear Him and He will show them
his
COV so this is okay the seet of the Lord
is with them that fear Him and we show
him this Covenant well let's find out
what the Covenant is first let's go into
Exodus the 24th
chapter read verses
26 and
28 say Exodus
24 Exodus 20 uh 34 Exodus
26 27 and 28 Exodus 3427 and 28
and the Lord said unto Moses write thou
these words for after the Ten of these
words I have made a covenant with thee
and with
Israel and he was there with the Lord 40
days and 40 nights he did neither eat
bread nor drink water and he wrote upon
the tables the words of the Covenant the
ten
commandments so now the Covenant is The
Ten Commandments right and uh this is a
big secret that don't nobody know about
it let's go into Matthew the 19th
Chapter read verses 16 and
17 read it when you get
there and behold one came and said unto
him good Master what good thing should I
do that may have eternal life he said
unto him why callest thou me good there
is none good but one that is God but if
thou will enter into life keep the
Commandments and that is a big secret
you keep God Commandments which is his
Covenant you going to get eternal life
yeah that's the secret Go the whole
world saying you ain't got to keep the
law
h through the big secret is simply keep
his Commandments and you will become God
yes
sir okay now let's look at the other one
read the other one the other one was
first corini
1 vers 7 and verse
27 read it for God have chosen the
foolish things of the world to confound
the wise and God have chosen the weak
things of the world to confound the
things which are
Mighty answer to that is I don't know
what they
are all
right somebody else want to make a
comment they can but I don't
know but those things
are all right
we're gonna leave it right there and um
keep it
moving uh yes do says on YouTube Cleo
dollar said 10% ties is no
longer after Jesus died and they only
used to tie once a year in other times
it was seven years of laying rest he
said weekly tying is not correct is this
right not like C ain't correct guest
caller what you
got I said you asking the wrong person
you need to go and ask Cleo dollar that
and then you ask him to show it to you
in the Bible where it's
written that you don't have to pay TI
anymore and that you only paid it once a
year or seven days you asking the wrong
person ask CLE
oala he made a statement tell him to go
to the scripture and prove it that's all
I have to say all right we gonna keep it
moving with the time Check Yes time is
835 Victorious mil asked in 2 Kings 20
verse2 when hazekiah turned his face to
the wall did that mean he face
Jerusalem Second Kings 20
and2 thought Hezekiah was already in
Jerusalem 2 Kings 20
and2 pick it up verse one read one and
two brother when you get
there in those days was Hezekiah sick
unto death and the prophet Isaiah the
son of amamos came to him and said unto
him thus say the Lord set thy house in
order for Thou shalt die and not
live and he turned his face to the wall
and prayed unto the Lord
saying all right
so it doesn't say here I mean he was
already in jerus it doesn't say which
wall he faced but he was already in
Jerusalem
so that's all I got anybody
else a nothing else to say all right
we're going to keep it moving from there
then sister Deborah
next yes uh James wine as is a New
Jerusalem coming down from heaven built
by human
hands New Jerusalem that's coming down
and Jesus said he go to prepare a place
is that is that built by human hands
brother Julius let's go to St John the
thir chapter and let the book answer
that
St John the thir
chapter
Jesus told
Nicodemus pick it up at verse three John
3 and he was uh one of the elders in
Israel John uh 3 and
3 go ahead tzel and Jesus answered and
said unto him ver very I say unto thee
except a man be born again he cannot see
the kingdom of God you don't be born
again till you get your glorified
body get down to verse
five and Jesus answered verely verely I
say unto thee except a man be born of
water and of the spirit he cannot enter
into the kingdom of God you got to be a
spirit being to be entered into the
kingdom of God so the answer is
absolutely no that is the Father's House
of many mansions New
Jerusalem has is not built by human
hands that's all I got all
right right yeah up in
heaven well read what Jesus said to uh
uh uh Nicodemus about who went to heaven
John 3 and pick it up at verse 12 and 13
if I have told you Earthly things ye
believe
not so how shall you believe if I tell
you of heavenly
things and no man have ascended up to
heaven but he that came down from heaven
even the son of man which is in heaven
so no
man
no no man is ascended to Heaven how then
can a flesh and blood person
build the Temple of the New Jerusalem
plus again in too if you go and read
about New Jerusalem you'll find out that
there ain't no temple in it in the first
place that is
right that's all I have to
say all right we hope that answered your
question there sister Deborah time check
as we move to our next yes the time is
8:39 Larry Smith asked can Satan cast
out demons to deceive these people to
follow
him uh no Satan about trying to get
demons cast in you he ain't about trying
to remove him let's uh let's read let's
go to um that
James the
um let's go to
um let's go to First Peter 5 first Peter
five
tanzel because anybody that got the
title of Serpent and devil and Satan and
dragon he is out to destroy everything
he can get his hands
on he ain't trying to cast no demons out
he trying to cast them in if he could
let's go into that uh first Peter 5 Rees
pick it up verse six go ahead brother
humble yourselves therefore under the
mighty hand of
God exalt you in due time yeah casting
all your care upon him for he carth for
you now read about um Satan there be
sober be vigilant because your adversary
the devil as a roaring lion walketh
about seeking whom he may devour he is
on his job of trying to devour you not
cast any Devils out and if he did that
hey his house couldn't stand let's go
into Matthew's 12 Matthew the 12th
chapter
and when you get there brother let's
pick it up at that verse
202 Matthew 12 and 22 go
ahead then was brought unto him one
possessed with the devil blind and dumb
and he healed him in so much that the
Blind and dumb both spake and saw yeah
it's the Lord here doing his healing now
not Satan go ahead and all the people
were amazed and said is not this the son
of David uhhuh but when the Pharisees
heard it they said for this fellow doth
not cast out Devils but by
beel the prince of the
Devils go ahead and Jesus knew their
thoughts and said unto them but every
Kingdom divided against itself is
brought to Desolation and every city or
house divided against itself should not
stand that's right when you do divid you
can't stand and what about Satan in this
last verse and if Satan cast out Satan
he is divided against himself how shall
then his kingdom stand wow so he's not
in the business of casting out devil
right he's about
destroying that is his whole job to
destroy so that's all I
got and we hope that that aned your
question as we continue to move on
sister de is time is ticking yes God
says God said in Acts 2 verse
17 young men will have visions so does
the Bible say the Visions will be like
the
vision uh Vision John and other prophets
had brother Dre can you share some light
on the
Visions yeah well let's just go to Acts
2 and
17 you know the prophets had visions and
John had visions and Revelations and so
let's read that verse 17 when you get it
go ahead brother and it shall come to
pass at the last days say God I will
pour out of my spirit upon All Flesh and
your sons and your daughters shall
prophesy and your young men shall see
visions and your old men shall dream
Dreams yeah so he said in the last days
this gonna happen right this is quot
from Joel the second chapter let's go to
Joel now Joel the 2 chapter and we gonna
read verse 30 and
31 and then we're gonna bag up he said
in the last days this gonna happen go
ahead Joel 2 and 30 30 and 31 go
ahead and I will show wonders in in the
heavens and in the earth blood and fire
and pillars of
smoke the the sun shall be turned into
darkness the moon and the blood before
the great and terrible day of the Lord
come now bag up and read verse 28 and
29 and it shall come to pass afterward
that I will pour out my spirit upon All
Flesh and your sons and your daughters
shall prophesies and your old men shall
dream dreams your young your young men
shall see
visions and also upon the servants and
upon the handmaids in those days will I
pour out my spirit so he say he gonna
pour His Spirit out which is his word
and his word will be prevalent will it
be like John and the prophets well let's
go to one other place let's go to uh
Isaiah the 11th chapter and we just
gonna read one verse there Isaiah
11 and read uh verse n but on your own
you could read from verse one to verse n
but we just going to read verse
n Go ahead brother they should not hurt
nor destroy in all my holy mouth for the
Earth shall be full of the knowledge of
the Lord as the water cover the sea yeah
because at that time the spirit of the
Lord is going to be poured on All Flesh
and the Earth will be full of the
knowledge of the Lord as the waters
cover the sea right yes
sir
indeed all right brother thank you for
that hope that answered their question
sister Deborah next one yes and moving
on time is ticking it's
8:45 uh Zion says I know you're supposed
to pray at least three times a day but I
struggle to do so because I find myself
repeating myself what exactly do I pray
about brother
Julius I've never read in the Bible
where you're supposed to pray three
times a day I know Daniel Prayed three
times a day we could read that in Daniel
6 and10 but uh you could pray Jesus said
pray without ceasing so you could pray
as many times a day as you want to let's
go to the more important thing also it's
not just uh and you said that uh you
struggle you said you struggle and you
said and to do so because you find
yourself repeating yourself let's do
what the how the Lord say do it let's go
to Matthew the 6th
chapter and I just want to hit the top
of these verses tanzel just to I want to
skim the top of this
verse pick it up at Matthew 6 and verse
5 just just them first four words go
ahead and when thou prayest that's
whenever you pray skip down to verse
six but thou when thou prayest he tell
you again verse
seven but when ye pray he's telling you
whenever you pray whenever you pray now
you want to know what the prayer about
try this one right here pick it up at
verse
n after this manner therefore pray ye
Our Father which are in heaven Hallowed
be thy name thy kingdom come thy will be
done in earth as it is in heaven yes
sir he going give us this day our daily
bread and forgive us of our debts as we
forgive our debt to us and lead us not
into temptation but Deliver Us from Evil
for thine is the kingdom and the power
and the glory forever that is the model
prayer that Jesus gave us on how to pray
and what to pray for and we have a
Israel of God have a lesson called The
Lord's Prayer get that lesson watch it
it is loaded with Benefits right more
than me I that's the best I can do
Corel all right thank you for that dear
brother as we keep moving sister Dev yes
David Williams asked for you to
explain first John 5 verse
S brother Dre can you do that for him
yes yes sir let's go to 1 John 5:7 and
read it when you get there read it
brother
tanzel for there are three that bear
record in heaven the Father the word and
the Holy Ghost and these three are one
yes sir what are they doing they are
bearing record in heaven right the
Father the word and the Holy Ghost and
these three are one in purpose but let's
go read it revelation
1 and verse one go ahead brother when
you get
it Revelation 1 and
one the revelation of Jesus Christ which
God gave unto him hold on tanzel that's
the revelation of Jesus Christ which the
father gave onto him that's two the
father is one Jesus Christ is two go
ahead to show unto his servants things
which must shortly come to pass M and he
sent and signified it by his
Angel unto his servant John so the angel
which is the third one that be record
gave it to John and then after the angel
gave it to John what did John do verse
two who bear record of the word of God
and of the testimony of Jesus Christ and
of all things that he saw so that's your
three that bear record in heaven the
Father the Son and the Holy Angel I hope
that helps right yes sir Dre as you said
earlier that that Holy Ghost is also an
angel yes sir all right brother hope
that answered their question next
question sister yes Lander as what makes
the King James version of the Bible
better a better transition uh
translation than other versions of the
Bible and what version the people in
Jesus day was
reading yes caller share some
light well there was no version of King
no version in King James in the days of
Jesus you only had the book of the
prophecy you didn't even have the New
Testament in the days of Jesus but I
want to say to this person we use the
King James version but you have
permission to use whatever version you
want to that is your right because God
made you a free agent so if you have a
version you think is better use it
that's all I have to say all right
Sister Sister Deborah next one yes
daughter of Judah as can the living pray
for the souls of those who have died and
didn't know the
truth brother
Julius answer is no the living cannot
pray for the souls of the people that
died let's go to Ecclesiastes the 3
chapter kzel Ecclesiastes
3 and we going to look at what the
wisest man that ever live according to
the Bible stated ecclesiast es 3 and
pick it up at verse
three Ecclesiastes 3 I'm sorry
Ecclesiastes uh 3 and pick it
up that's not what I want I want
Ecclesiastes
9 can't read my own writing Ecclesiastes
3 and N nine and three I'm sorry nine
and three there you go Ecclesiastes N9
and three when you get it go ahead
brother
this is an evil among all things that
are done under the son uhuh there is one
even unto all yeah also the heart of the
sons of men is full of evil uhhuh
Madness is in their heart while they
live while they live go ahead and after
that they go to the dead
uhhuh for to him that is joined to all
the living there is hope uhuh a living
dog is better than a dead line so you
could pray for somebody that's gone mad
while they're alive you could pray for
anybody while they're alive but what the
book says at verse five but the living
know that they shall die but the dead
know not anything the dead know not
anything go ahead neither have they any
more reward for the memory of them is
forgotten because they memory stops you
sleep you're dead go ahead also their
love and their hatred and their Envy is
now perished uhuh neither have there
anymore portion forever in anything that
is done under the sun because once you
dead you once you sleep you are dead and
you don't hear you don't see and there's
no consciousness in the grave where thou
goest so no you cannot Pray For Dead
Souls oh that's right brother spend that
time working out your own salvation with
fear and trembling that's right brother
all right next question
sister uh she also asked the 12 tribes
of Israel came from Jacob's two wives
Rachel and Leah and his two concubines
uh BHA and
Zar does that justify today's Hebrew
Israelite men to have multiple
wives yes caller
let's go and read what God told the king
whatever he told the king that said over
you is for
everybody let's go into Deuteronomy the
17th chapter read verses 16 and
17 Deuteronomy
176 and
17 but he should not multiply horses to
himself nor cause the people to return
to Egypt to the end that he should
multiply horses for as much as the Lord
have said unto you ye shall henceforth
return no more that way neither shall he
multiply wife to himself that his heart
turn not away neither shall he greatly
multiply to himself silver and gold
that's enough that's enough but the big
thing he said neither shall he multiply
wives unto himself this is the king and
that goes for people too why because you
going to be on you're going to be
thinking about about these women and
they you going to be involved in them
instead of being in the word of God and
anything more than one is
multiplication and you want to be a
servant of God then let's go into First
Timothy the 3 chapter and read verse
two first Timothy
3 and
two i b you then must be blameless the
husband of one wife Vigilant sober of
good behavior given to hospitality at to
teach now is a bishop these brothers run
around he call themselves on count of
titles he said the husband of one wife
go to titles the one and
six if any be blameless the husband of
one wife having faithful children not
accused of r or
unruly these are the ones that should
serve God husband and one
wife plus the book tell you to obey the
laws of the land and this land and a
whole lot of other lands say a man can't
have but one wife right anything more
than that they call it polygamy ver
again too you walking around with the
arre of women and you trying to teach
the word of God ain't nobody going to
hear a word that you say the answer is
no all right hope that answered your
question next question sister yes and
the last question that daughter of Judah
asked is for you to explain first corini
10 verses 25-
27 First Corinthians 10 let's go to 10
zel pick it up at that verse 25 Guess
call let take it from there 1
Corinthians 10 and verse
25 whoever is so in the shable that eat
asking no question for conscience sake
for the Earth is the Lord's and the
fullness
thereof any of them that believe not be
you to a feast and ye be disposed to go
whatsoever is set before you eat asking
no questions for conscious
say now I might not ask no questions for
conscience sake but I sure will ask some
questions for salvation sake are you
going to put something before me I don't
know what it is for my salvation sake
I'm going to ask you why do I say that
let's go into Leviticus the 20th
chapter and read 23 and Skip down and
read
25 Leviticus 20 when you get there pick
it up at that verse 23 10
there and you shall not and ye shall not
walk in the manner of the Nations which
I cast out before you for they committed
all these things and therefore I AB
horded
them I skip down to 25
you shall therefore put difference
between clean beast and unclean and
between unclean fowls and clean and you
shall not make your souls abominable by
Beast or by foul or by any manner of
living things that creep on the ground
which I have separated from you as
unclean so for salvation sake I asked
what is this if I don't know what it is
right and what I really mean is for
salvation sake Look What the Lord say he
going to do the people that deal with
certain things let's go to Isaiah 66 and
read verses 15-1
17 Isaiah
66 take it up there verse 15 and read
down to the
17 for behold the Lord will come with
fire and with his chariots like a
whirlwind to render his anger with Fury
and his rebuke with flames of fire for
by fire and by his sword will the Lord
plead with All Flesh and the slain of
the Lord shall be many and they that
sanctify themselves and purify
themselves in the garden behind one tree
in the midst eating swine flesh and the
Abomination and the mouse shall be
consumed together sayeth the
Lord now so you put something on a table
and I don't know what it is
for conscious sake like Paul said your
conscious I won't ask but for my
salvation sake I'm going to say what is
this right that's all I have to
say all right sister deorah time check
time is nine
o'clock all right well we have ran out
of
time and we like to thank everybody from
all around the world who sent in all
those questions and we took Joy
answering them with you so we saying if
you submitted a question and we didn't
get to it don't resubmit it sister deah
would take it put it in rotation and we
will answer your question next week if
possible so until we all come together
again hey be safe be blessed and may the
Lord have mercy on us all close us out
brother
tanel Our Father which are in heaven
Hallowed be thy name
thy kingdom come thy will be done in
earth as it is in heaven give us this
day our daily bread and forgive us of
our debts as we forgive our
debtors and lead us not into temptation
but Deliver Us from Evil for thine is
the kingdom and the power and the glory
forever in Jesus name we pray amen
amen good night all